A Guide to the Office of the Messrs. Rockefeller records, Religious Interests, Series N FA323
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Baptist Organizations
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - Report on a Survey of Fifty-Eight Organizations of the Northern Baptist Denomination, June 1925 (Box 8, Folder 57A)
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - General, 1926-1932 (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - General, 1933-1935, 1939, 1945-1948, 1958-1959 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - Gift of April 27, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 60)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s gift toward re-establishment of destroyed buildings. Gift to World Emergency Forward Fund. Correspondents include Earl F. Adams, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Arthur W. Packard.
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Letter, March 1935, 1934-1936 (Box 9, Folder 61)
    Photostat of letters and copies, 1935. Proposed letter withdrawing support, 1934-1935. Drafts, criticisms made, copy of final letter sent. Correspondents include Trevor Arnett, Raymond B. Fosdick, E. L. Ballard, J. B. Colgate, T. J. Ross, Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, Albert L. Scott. Publicity, 1935-1936. Newspaper articles, distribution of letter, publicity in Watchman-Examiner, criticism of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. Correspondents include Robert W. Gumbel, T. J. Ross, Harcourt Parrish. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s Letter, 1935-1936. John D. Rockefeller, Jr. acknowledged letters, letters of appreciation. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Robert W. Gumbel, T. J. Ross, and Helen Spencer.
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - Baptist Board of Promotion, 1920-1930, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 62)
    Trevor Arnett's and Raymond B. Fosdick's survey of finances of Board and its affiliated Boards and agencies, convention in Chicago, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution towards convention expenses. Various pledges. Rev. Johnston Myers' salary, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution. Correspondents include E. L. Ballard, Willard S. Richardson, C. Woelfkin, Trevor Arnett, Raymond B. Fosdick, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Harry Fosdick, Johnston Myers, W. H. Bowler.
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - Controversy with Park Avenue Baptist Church, 1925-1926 (Box 9, Folder 63)
    Baptist Bible Union "Resolution on the Rockefeller-Fosdick Conspiracy to destroy the Baptist Denomination;" protests against seating Park Avenue Church delegation at Seattle Convention, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s congratulations to Dr. Woelfkin for his address at convention, resolutions expressing disapproval of Church with Church reply. Correspondents include C. Woelfkin, A. W. Armour, H. E. Fosdick, J. B. Colgate, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - Laymen's Campaign, 1917-1934, 1941 (Box 10, Folder 64)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s attendance at Baptist Laymen's luncheon, pleasure at Mr. Coleman's ideas. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contributions, $1,000,000 Campaign, 1919 Victory Campaign. Correspondents include Charles O. Heydt, E. L. Ballard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., C. M. Pratt, E. M. Johnson, William Rockefeller, Willard S. Richardson, F. W. Ayer, F. P. Haggard, Starr J. Murphy, W. C. Coleman, W. G. Conklin.
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - Ministers and Missionaries Benefit Board, 1911-1921 (Box 10, Folder 65)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pledge to Fund, statement of manner in which funds were used. List of special gifts from John D. Rockefeller. Gifts from John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller, pledge May 4, 1937 for test study of churches in Connecticut. Pensions; pension for Rev. Mangano. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., E. V. Cary, H. L. Morehouse, Frederick T. Gates, P. C. Wright, Willard S. Richardson, W. H. Bowler, Thomas M. Debevoise, Trevor Arnett, E. T. Tomlinson, Starr J. Murphy, Antonio Mangano.
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - Ministers and Missionaries Benefit Board, 1922-1939 (Box 10, Folder 66)
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - Ministers and Missionaries Benefit Board, 1939, 1943-1945, 1949-1950, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 67)
  - Baptist Organizations - Northern Baptist Convention - World Mission Crusade, 1945-1947 (Box 10, Folder 68)
    New and supplementary data for John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s consideration in connection with World Mission Crusade of Northern Baptist Convention. Correspondents include Luther Wesley Smith, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Baptist Organizations - Southern Baptist Convention - General, 1920-1949 (Box 11, Folder 69)
    Activities of Relief and Annuity Board, 1924-1930. Application of further contributions, death of Dr. Lunsford, John D. Rockefeller's gift. John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution to Board on behalf of father. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, C. Woelfkin, William Lunsford, John D. Rockefeller, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Thomas J. Watts, N. Davis, Robert W. Gumbel.
  - Baptist Organizations - Southern Baptist Convention - Home and Foreign Mission Boards (Box 11, Folder 70)
    Reports of activities of Boards, copies of charter, constitution and bylaws, John D. Rockefeller's gift to Board, to Judson Centennial Fund. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Starr J. Murphy, Rev. George W. Truett, Willard S. Richardson, S. J. Porter, T. B. Roy, Dr. Burton.
  - Baptist Organizations - Rev. and Mrs. Richard Hartley, 1908-1913 (Box 11, Folder 71)
    Mr. Hartley's ill health, John D. Rockefeller's personal donations, Church financial difficulties, denominational situation on Manhattan Island, Dr. Hartley's death, aid for his widow. Correspondents include Rev. Richard Hartley, John D. Rockefeller, Frederick T. Gates, Starr J. Murphy, E. V. Cary, Edward Judson.
- Bible Societies
  - Bible Societies - General, 1925-1926, 1939-1961 (Box 11, Folder 72)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s contribution to National Bible Institute, earmarking of gift to Jerry McAuley Cremoine Mission, renewal of contribution, New York Bible Society dinner - Nelson A. Rockefeller speaker. Correspondents include Dana S. Creel, Arthur W. Packard.
    File Plan note
    52
  - Bible Societies - General, 1942-1959 (Box 11, Folder 72A)
  - Bible Societies - National Bible Institute, 1925-1952 (Box 11, Folder 73)
    Needs, appeals. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Thomas B. Appleget, Arthur W. Packard.
  - Bible Societies - American Bible Society, 1917-1946 (Box 11, Folder 74)
    Contributions by members of Rockefeller family, work of Society, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s pledge to War Emergency Fund and Tarrytown and Pocantico Hills campaign, gift of John D. Rockefeller's 1587 Geneva Bible to Society. Laurance S. Rockefeller gift. Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, Arthur W. Packard, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Dana S. Creel, Morris Shepherd.
    52.2
  - Bible Societies - American Bible Society, 1947-1962 (Box 11, Folder 75)
  - Bible Societies - Bible Seminary of New York, 1902, 1909, 1917-1956 (Box 12, Folder 76)
    Request for contribution from Bible Teachers Training School, pleasure at Dr. White's work. Correspondents include Starr J. Murphy, Willard S. Richardson, J. Campbell White, Thomas B. Appleget, Wilbert W. White.
    52.3
- Christian Publications
  - Christian Publications, 1920-1927 (Box 12, Folder 77)
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s donation toward publication of American Encyclopedia of Christianity. John D. Rockefeller's purchase of set of "Outline of Christianity." Correspondents include Willard S. Richardson, John D. Rockefeller, Jr., G. E. Vincent, Raymond B. Fosdick, Charles O. Heydt.
    5
- Church Unity Radio Address
  - Church Unity Radio Address, 1937 (Box 12, Folder 78)
    Copy of John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s address urging church unity. Comments on address. Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., John D. Rockefeller, Robert W. Gumbel.
    219
  - Church Unity Radio Address - Responses (A-E), 1937 (Box 12, Folder 79)
  - Church Unity Radio Address - Responses (F-Mac), 1937 (Box 12, Folder 80)
  - Church Unity Radio Address - Responses (M-P), 1937 (Box 12, Folder 81)
  - Church Unity Radio Address - Responses (R-Z), 1937 (Box 12, Folder 82)
- Churches
  - Churches - Miscellaneous
    John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s gifts: Gloucester, Massachusetts carillon, Cleveland organ, Sartell Prentice's Nyack Plan, Norwegian Seamen's Church, Puerto Rican Baptist Church, Brotherhood of St. Andrew, Methodist Church, Harford Mills with memorial window, New Bethel Church, Ormond, Florida, South Ferry Church Memorial Society, Church of the Magdalene, Pocantico Corpus Christi 40th Anniversary, Canterbury Cathedral. John D. Rockefeller gifts to Cleveland and New York churches. Family gifts to Cleveland Heights Presbyterian, Colonial Church, Bayside, New York, Christ Episcopal, Tarrytown. Many declinations, some small gifts in recent material retained.
    Correspondents include John D. Rockefeller, Jr., Willard S. Richardson, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Dana S. Creel, Arthur W. Packard, Thomas M. Debevoise, Robert W. Gumbel, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller, Nelson A. Rockefeller, David Rockefeller.
    - Churches - Miscellaneous (A-L), 1896-1936 (Box 13, Folder 83)
      *Alexander Avenue Baptist Church, New York City, 1898-1935 Brotherhood of St. Andrew, 1923 Christ Church, Tarrytown, New York, 1934 *Christ Episcopal Church, Tarrytown, New York, 1934-1944 Christian Union, Forest, Ohio, 1905 Church of the Epiphany, New York City, 1935-1961 Dominican Fathers, Hawthorne, New York, 1933 Fairmount Methodist Church, Cleveland, Ohio, 1903-1911 First Baptist Church, Bedford, Ohio, 1906 First Baptist Church, Cleveland, Ohio, 1902 First Baptist Church, Mt. Vernon, New York, 1905 First Baptist Church, Puerto Rico, 1928 *First German Baptist Church, Cleveland, Ohio, 1902-1916 *Cleveland Heights Presbyterian Church (Forest Hills Church), Cleveland Heights, Ohio, 1909-1951 Free Baptist Church, Wolfeboro Falls, New Hampshire, 1928 Grace Cathedral, San Francisco, California, 1929-1957 Frank W. La Bar (Reverend), Adirondacks, New York, 1928-1931 Lakeview Church, Cleveland, Ohio, 1896-1909 Lakewood Methodist Church, New Jersey, 1912-1916 Minerva Mission, New York City, 1929 Sixth Street Baptist Church, Lakewood, New Jersey, 1913
      An asterisk (*) indicates church received Rockefeller contribution.
    - Churches - Miscellaneous (M-Z), 1896-1936 (Box 13, Folder 84)
      Rep. A. Piatt Andrews (re: Portuguese Church), Washington, DC, 1922 Holy Family Roman Catholic Church, New York City, 1949-1953 Madison Avenue M.E. Church, New York City, New York 1931 Mt. Airy Presbyterian Church, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania 1931 *North Baptist Church, New York City, 1905-1942 Norwegian Sailors' Home, New York City, 1927 Nyack Plan, Nyack, New York, 1926 Our Lady of Blessed Sacrament, Cleveland, Ohio, 1923 Rockefeller Memorial Church, Syracuse, New York, 1933 St. Alban's Church, Cleveland, Ohio 1911 St. Catherine de Sienna Church, New York City, 1930 St. Catherine's Priory, New York City, New York, 1930 *St. George's Church, New York City, 1925-1961 St. Mark's Episcopal Church, Cleveland, Ohio 1901 St. Paul's Church, Cleveland, Ohio, 1901-1906 St. Paul's Church, London, England, 1922-1926 *Siloam Presbyterian Church, New York City, 1929-1961 Trinity Congregational Church, Cleveland, Ohio, 1903 Westminster Presbyterian Church, Cleveland, Ohio 1916
    - Churches - Miscellaneous - Rev. J. H. H. Darling, 1933-1936 (Box 13, Folder 85)
      Rev. J. H. Darling (see Presbyterian Church, Lakewood, New Jersey), 1933-1936; First Presbyterian Church, Lakewood, New Jersey (donated to), 1906
    - Churches - Miscellaneous (A-F), 1937-1950 (Box 13, Folder 86)
      Altweid bei Neuweid, Germany, 1961 Andover Newton Theological School, Newton Centre, Massachusetts, 1945 Augustana Evangelical Lutheran Church, Minneapolis, Minnesota, 1950 Bethany Christian Church, Virginia, 1950 Beverly Farms Baptist Church, Beverly, Massachusetts, 1935 Brown Memorial Baptist Church, Brooklyn, New York, 1949 Canterbury Cathedral, London, England, 1946 Canterbury Catholic Church, 1947 Central Baptist Church, Providence, Rhode Island, 1943 Christ Methodist Church, New York City, 1945-1946 Church of God by Faith, Ormond, Florida, 1937 Church of Heavenly Rest, New York City, 1946 Church of the Holy Martyrs, Port union, Newfoundland, 1948 Church of the Living God, Buellton, California, 1945 Collegeside Congregational Church, Nashville, Tennessee, 1945 Congregational Church, Manhasset, New York, 1947 Connor Avenue Baptist Church, Joplin, Missouri, 1945 Coptic Orthodox Church, New York City, 1946 Corpus Christi, New York City, 1945 Edgewood Congregational Church, Rhode Island, 1950 Fellowship Church, Orono, Maine, 1930 Fifth Avenue Presbyterian Church, New York City, 1950 First Baptist Church, Dayton, Ohio, 1948 First Baptist Church, Whiting, Indiana, 1940 First Baptist Church, Stearns, Kentucky, 199 First Church in Plymouth, Plymouth, Massachusetts, 1948 First Congregational Church, Burlington, Iowa, 1938 First Congregational Church, Woodstock, Connecticut, 1939 First Evangelical Lutheran Church, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 1931 First Italian Baptist Church, New York City, 1940-1949 First Presbyterian Church, Elizabeth, New Jersey 1947 First Presbyterian Church, Seattle, Washington, 1933 Reverend G. A. Foster, Delaware (see Newark Union Church), 1952 Friendship Baptist Church, Atlanta, Georgia, 1943 National Study of the Negro Church, New York City, New York, 1949 New Ark Union Church, Wilmington, Delaware, 1950 St. John's Church, Hampton, Virginia, 1950
    - Churches - Miscellaneous (G-O), 1937-1950 (Box 13, Folder 87)
      Rev. W. Armstrong (Methodist missionary of State of New Jersey), Jersey City, New Jersey, 1940 Church of Our Lady of Victory, New York City, New York, 1946 First Baptist Church, Ontario, Canada, 1942 Friendship House, Albany, New York, 1944 Good Shepherd - Faith \Presbyterian Church, New York City, 1946-1960 Greeenwood Avenue Methodist Church, Trenton, New Jersey, 1941 Holy Cross Church, Tarrytown, New York, 1943 Indiana Council of Churches, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1945 *Jan Hus Presbyterian Church, New York City, 1940-1953 Japanese Methodist Church; Dutch Reformed Church, New York City, 1952-1953 Jefferson Street Baptist Church, Roanoke, Virginia, 1931 Manor Community Church House, New York City, 1938-1951 Mt. Desert Island, Manset, Maine, 1940 Mt. Olive Baptist Church, Cushing, Oklahoma, 1949 Mt. Pleasant Baptist Church, Pleasantville, New Jersey, 1940 Mt. Washington Presbyterian Church, New York City, 1941 New Bethel A.M.E. Church, Ormond, Florida, 1934-1937 New Hope Institutional Baptist Church, Tarrytown, New York, 1946-1950 Old Knox Church, Thomaston, Maine, 1950 Our Lady of Victory, New York City, 1946 Scottish-American Religious Fund, New Deer, Scotland, 1951 Unnamed Olneyville, Rhode Island Church, 1931
    - Churches - Miscellaneous (G-O), 1950 (Box 13, Folder 87A)
      Hyde Park Methodist Church, Tampa, Florida, 1950
    - Churches - Miscellaneous (P-Z), 1911-1950 (Box 14, Folder 88)
      African Methodist Episcopal Church, Ormond, 1939 Baptist Church, Pamplica, North Carolina, 1949 Baptist Church (two unnamed), Pueblo, Colorado, 1940 Baptist Church, Seaford, Delaware, 1949 Board of Christian Education Presbyterian Church, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1946 Christ Church Boys Club, Tarrytown, New York, 1947 Christ Episcopal Church, Tarrytown, 1934-1944 Congregational Church of Richford, New York, 1937 Church of the Open Door, Wellesley Hills, Massachusetts, 1947 Lake Avenue Baptist Church, Pueblo, Colorado, 1940 Norwood Presbyterian Church, New Jersey, 1941 Plymouth Church, New York City, New York, 1946 Presbyterian Church in the USA (United Presbyterian Foundation), New York City, 1952-1960 Presbyterian Church of Norwood, New Jersey, 1941 Pilgrim Congregational Church, Birmingham, Alabama, 1950 Richford Congregational Church, New York 1938 Rock Church, New York City, 1940 St. Bartholomew's Church, New York City, 1948-1954 St. John's Church, Milbank, South Dakota, 1947 St. Mark's Church in the Bouwerie, New York City, 1947-1958 St. Mary's Free Will Baptist Church, New Bern, North Carolina 1949 St. Michael Syrian Greek Orthodox Church, New York, 1946-1951 St. Paul's A.M.E. Church, Ormond Beach, Florida St. Theresa's Holy Name Society, Tarrytown, New York, 1943-1958 St. Teresa's Rectory, Tarrytown, New York, 1942 St. Thomas' Church, Mamaroneck, New York, 1942 Saugatuck Congregational Church, Westport, Connecticut, 1952 Shaw Temple A.M.E. Zion Church, Atlanta, Georgia, 1947 Shiloh Baptist Church, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1949-1952 South Ferry Church Memorial Society, 1940 Southwestern Presbyterian Church, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 1931 Syrian Orthodox Church of Malabar, India, 1950 Tremont Baptist Church, New York City, 1949 United Churchof South India, Saint Louis, Missouri, 1950 Wall Street Synagogue, New York City, 1945-1959 Western Presbyterian Church, Washington, D.C., 1933 West Side Presbyterian Church, Ridgewood, New Jersey, 1948 World Friendship House, Boston, Massachusetts, 1947-1960
    - Churches - Miscellaneous, 1950-1954 (Box 14, Folder 88A)
      St. Bartholomew's Church, New York City, 1948-1954 First Baptist Church, Tennessee, 1951 First Baptist Church, Gatlinburg, Tennessee, 1951 Syrian Orthodox Church of Malabar, Malabar, India, 1950
    - Churches - Miscellaneous, 1951 (Box 14, Folder 89)
      Baptist Church, Bassett, Virginia, 1951 Baptist Church of the Master, Cleveland, Ohio 1951 Claybrook Baptist Church, Virginia, 1951 *Colonial Church of Bayside, New York, 1951 Rt. Rev. W. E. Conkling, Bishop of Chicago, 1951 Episcopal Church, Chicago, Illinois 1951 First Baptist Church, Elmsford, New York, 1951-1958 First Baptist Church of Cambridge, Cambridge, Massachusetts, 1951 First Methodist Church, Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, 1951 Judson Memorial Church, New York City, 1950-1951 Keene Valley Congregational Church, New York, 1946-1951 Kentucky Annual Conference of the Methodist Church, 1951 Margarita Union Church, Panama Canal Zone, 1951 Palompon Church Philippines, 1951-1952 St. Alban's Church, New York City, 1911 St. Clemen's Church, Hannover, Germany, 1951 St. Hyacinth Church, Cleveland, Ohio, 1951-1961 St. John the Baptist Catholic Church, Minnesota, 1951 St. John's Episcopal Church, Fisher's Island, New York, 1951-1961 St. Pancras Church, London, England, 1951 Shawomet Baptist Church, Rhode Island, 1950-1951 Shiloh Seventh Day Adventist Church, Virginia, 1951 United Church of Christ in the Philippines, 1951-1960 World Mission, Inc., New York City, 1951
    - Churches - Miscellaneous, 1952-1953 (Box 14, Folder 90)
      *Abington Church, Virginia, 1952-1954 Baptist Church, Cap-Haitien, Haiti, 1952 Beacon Light Seventh Day Adventist Church, Missouri, 1952 Christ Church, Philadelphia, 1952-1959 Church of God in Christ, Albany, New York, 1952 Ellinwood Church, Philippines, 1952 1st Calvary Baptist Church, New York, 1956 1st Church of Christ Scientist, Tarrytown, New York 1953 1st Covenant Church, Livingston, New Jersey, 1953 First Lutheran Church, Albany, New York, 1953 1st Presbyterian Church, Far Rockaway, New York, 1953-1955 1st Presbyterian Church, Uleta, Florida, 1953 Grace Church, New York City, 1952 Greater Hood Memorial African Methodist Episcopal Church, New York City, 1952 Hepzibah Baptist Church, Pennsylvania, 1952 Holy Name of Jesus Church, Scranton, Pennsylvania, 1952 Holy Water of Jordan, Inc. (Greek Patriarchate of Jerusalem), 1953 Independent Church of the Philippines, 1952 Mathewson Street Church, Providence, Rhode Island, 1952 Memorial Presbyterian Church, St. Augustine, Florida, 1952 *Middle Smithfield Presbyterian Church (Mrs. J. Richards), 1952 Mt. Zion Baptist Church, New York City, 1953 Pilgrim Baptist Church, New York City, New York, 1951-1952 Presbyterian Church in the United States of American (United Presbyterian Foundation), New York City, 1952-1960 St. James Church, New York City, 1953 St Mark's Methodist Church, New York City, 1952 St. Mary's Church, Closter, New Jersey, 1953 St. Peter's Episcopal Church, New York City, 1952 Union Baptist Church, Mystic, Connecticut, 1952-1958 United Church of Los Alamos, New Mexico, 1953 United Church of Raleigh, Institute of Religion, North Carolina, 1953 University Baptist Church, Tucson, Arizona, 1953 Village Presbyterian Church and Village Temple, New York City, 1952-1955 West Side Christian Parish, Chicago, Illinois, 1953 *Williams Institutional Colored Methodist Episcopal Church, New York City, 1953-1960
    - Churches - Miscellaneous (A-M), 1954-1955 (Box 14, Folder 91)
      Dr. C. H. Ancrum, New York City, 1954 Aquia Church, Stafford, Virginia, 1954 Bethany Baptist Church, New York City, 1955 *Bethel Baptist Church, Mt. Kisco, New York, 1954 Bethel Pentecostal Tabernacle, New Jersey, 1955 Canadian Journal of Theology (Baptist Convention of Ontario and Quebec), 1953 Cathedral of the Pines, Rindge, New Hampshire, 1954-1961 Christ Church, Methodist, New York City, New York, 1954 Christ Divine Healing Church, Liberia, 1955 Church in Radburn, New Jersey, 1954-1961 Church in the Garden, Long Island, New York, 1954 Church of the Mediator, Allentown, Pennsylvania, 1955 Church of the Sea and Land, New York City, 1955 Eastwood Parish Church, England, 1955 *1st Church of Christ, Farmington, Connecticut, 1955 1st Lutheran Church, Plymouth, Ohio 1954 Free Church at Findon, England, 1954 Holy Innocence Church, 1954 Rev. C. M. Hunt, New Rochelle, New York, 1955 Madison Avenue Baptist Church, New York City, 1955-1956 Methodist Missionary Episcopal Church, New Jersey, 1940-1955
    - Churches - Miscellaneous - David Rockefeller, 1949-1960 (Box 14, Folder 91A)
      American Catholic Memorial Church, Paris, 1954 Asbury Methodist Church, Tarrytown, New York, 1954 Community Church, Chapel Hill, North Carolina, 1953 Diocese of Natchez, Mississippi, 1951-1952 1st Baptist Church, Elmsford, New York, 1951-1958 The Foundation of the Presbyterian Church USA, New York City, New York, 1957 Judson Memorial Church, New York City, 1950-1951 A Men's Association of the South Presbyterian Church, Dobbs Ferry, New York, 1949 St. Bartholomew's Church, New York City, 1948-1954 St. Bartholomew's Church, White Plains, New York, 1952 Wall Street Synagogue, New York City, 1945-1959 World Friendship House, Boston, Massachusetts, 1947-1960
    - Churches - Miscellaneous (N-Z), 1954-1955 (Box 15, Folder 92)
      New First Baptist Church, New York City, 1955 New York Port Society and Mariners' Church, 1954 Northminster Presbyterian, Indianapolis, Indiana, 1955 Ormond Beach Methodist Church, 1954 Philippine Independent Catholic Church, 1955-1960 Pilgrim Congregational Church, Massachusetts, 1954 St. Andrew's Church of Scotland, Liverpool, 1955 St. Martin-in-the-Fields, Georgia, 1954 St. Roque Church, Paraguay, 1955 St. Thomas Rectory, Dover-Foxcroft, Masachusetts, 1955 Saint's Temple Church of God in Christ, New York City, 1955 St. Thomas Rectory, Dover-Foxcroft, Massachusetts, 1955 Shiloh Baptist Church, New Rochelle, New York, 1955 Shrine of the Ages, Arizona, 1955-1959 Father Thibodeau, Maine, 1954 Trinity Episcopal Church, Fishkill, New York, 1955 Union Church, Lima, Peru, 1955 Unionville Christian Church, Virginia, 1955 Wesleyan Methodist Church, Hartville, Ohio, 1954 Windermere Presbyterian Church, Cleveland, Ohio, 1916-1954 Wooden Church Crusade, Germany
    - Churches - Miscellaneous, 1956-1957 (Box 15, Folder 93)